(Bernadette:)I like your suit.
(Penny:)Oh, thanks. Got a couple
new outfits for work.
(Howard:)How does it feel knowing
your fiancée's job
(Howard:)is to go out
and flirt with doctors,
(Howard:)looking like that,
while you sit here, you know...
(Howard:)looking like this?
(Leonard:)She doesn't flirt
with doctors.
(Penny:)Yeah. It's all
very professional.
(Amy:)You know when you bend over,
I can see down your shirt?
(Penny:)Okay, good.
(Bernadette:)Speaking of new careers,
how are things going
(Bernadette:)with dark matter,
Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yeah, I'd have to say
it's the most exiting time
(Sheldon:)in the history of the field.
Oh.
(Bernadette:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)I started doing it.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
You know, the government funded
(Raj:)the biggest experiment yet
to detect dark matter.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yeah,
(Leonard:)I've read about that--
they're sending research teams
(Leonard:)down into abandoned salt mines.
You know, Sheldon,
(Raj:)if we apply to be
one of those teams,
(Raj:)we could be
on the ground floor
of something big--
(Raj:)not just for theoretical physics
but for astrophysics as well.
(Penny:)Wait, hang on-- you guys
are gonna work in a mine?
(Sheldon:)Why not?
You had
(Penny:)a panic attack when
we went through the car wash.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps the emotion
you're referring to was shock
(Sheldon:)at you having something cleaned.
(Leonard:)I think what Penny meant is,
the thought of you two
(Leonard:)in a mine is kind of funny--
it's like a cat riding a Roomba.
(laughs)
(Howard:)If they get scared,
they'll have those hats
(Howard:)with the lights on them,
'cause down there
it's night-night all the time!
(Bernadette:)Maybe they could
(Bernadette:)ride around in one of
those mine carts that go,
(squeakily):
ee-oo-ee-oo-ee-oo.
(Leonard:)Yeah, it'll help them get away
when they see a gh-gh-ghost...!
(Sheldon:)Are they making
fun of us?
Yup.
(Sheldon:)I miss the old days
when I couldn't tell.